[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "When a wave of light with a wavelength of approximately 700 nm hits your eyes, it causes sensation of what color?", "correct_answer": "Red", "incorrect_answers": ["Green", "Black", "It will cause no sensation"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which character from the 1939 movie Gone with the Wind utters the phrase As God is my witness, Ill never be hungry again?", "correct_answer": "Scarlett OHara", "incorrect_answers": ["Rhett Butler", "Ashley Wilkes", "Melanie Hamilton"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the 1974 movie Earthquake, they lower people down from an office building by a chair attached to what material?", "correct_answer": "A fire hose", "incorrect_answers": ["Wires", "They dropped them", "Rope"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What couple gets married at the end of the movie Clueless?", "correct_answer": "Miss Geist and Mr. Hall", "incorrect_answers": ["Cher and Josh", "Dionne and Murray", "Tai and Travis"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Although he is known primarily as a physicist, Albert Einstein did make at least one very important contribution to modern mathematics. In which field was this contribution?", "correct_answer": "Tensor analysis", "incorrect_answers": ["Differential topology", "Theory of groups", "Partial differential equations"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In his works, this Greek playwright, whose contribution to the theater was the addition of a second actor to the scenes, focused on mans position in the cosmos, in relation to the gods.", "correct_answer": "Aeschylus", "incorrect_answers": ["Thucydidies", "Sophocles", "Euripides"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The worlds largest swimming pool in 2007 was in this country.", "correct_answer": "Chile", "incorrect_answers": ["Morocco", "North Korea", "Venezuela"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Approximately how tall is a grizzly bear when standing on its hind legs?", "correct_answer": "8 feet (2.4 m)", "incorrect_answers": ["9 feet (2.7 m)", "7 feet (2.1 m)", "6 feet (1.8 m)"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which is the largest planet in the Solar System?", "correct_answer": "Jupiter", "incorrect_answers": ["Mars", "Saturn", "Venus"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the occupation of Daniel Day-Lewis character Newland Archer in the 1993 romantic drama movie The Age of Innocence, directed by Martin Scorsese?", "correct_answer": "Lawyer", "incorrect_answers": ["Banker", "Businessman", "Painter"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Actor Johnny Crawford was born March 26, 1947.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The first European to explore the Chesapeake Bay surrounded by modern day Maryland and Virginia was the Italian Giovanni da Verrazzano.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}]